<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- example file containing base tags -->

<game>	
	<title>Paul Hero: End Polio Now!</title>
	<founding-date>2012</founding-date>
	<website>www.criosdevs.com</website>
	<based-in>Mendoza, Argentina, 2012</based-in>
	
	<press-contact>contact@criosdevs.com</press-contact>

	<socials>
		<social>
			<name>twitter.com/CriosDevs</name>
			<link>www.twitter.com/CriosDevs</link>
		</social>
		<social>
			<name>facebook.com/PaulHeroEPN</name>
			<link>www.facebook.com/PaulHeroepn</link>
		</social>
		<social>
			<name>facebook.com/CriosDevs</name>
			<link>www.facebook.com/CriosDevs</link>
		</social>

	</socials>

	<description>	
		Paul Hero is an adventure platfomer where you can be the intrepid Paul and fight against the polio by avoiding obstacles, testing your reflexes, defying the laws of gravity and delivering vaccines to eradicate this horrible disease in the world.
	</description>	
		
	<histories>
		
		<history>
			<header>Test your reflexes and overcome the challenges in this 2D platformer puzzle adventure. Embark with Paul on his adventures and combats polio delivering the vaccines sent by Rotary International.</header>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>Paul is an adventurer who offers his help to whoever needs it. That is why when Rotary International organization asks him to exterminate the polio (a horrible disease) in a remote island of the Pacific, he accepts without hesitation. Rotary has spent years of fighting to eradicate the disease of the world and still there are a few zones affected, the island is one of them. Unfortunately, those that have gone there to take the medicine...never returned. </text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>Our adventurer boards the plain full of boxes with vaccine against the polio. After a few hours of flight, he sees the island but something between the shadows with a mask, which has the form of skull, raise its hands and a lightning strikes the plane.</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>Fortunately, Paul gets out of it with his parachute while he sees how the boxes with the vaccine fall down in different sites of the island. When he lands on, he notices that there are various traps to keep away the outsiders that want to help the residents. Paul has to find the way of delivering the vaccines and get out of the island alive!</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>						
			<header>How Paul hero: end polio now started.</header>
			<text>Early in 2014, Rotary International decided to gather a group of clubs in Argentina with the name Rotary Distritict 4849. Due to expand the work of Rotary worldwide, the District contacted Crios Devs in order to make a video game that would be free, accessible, fun and catch the attention of the public towards the organization and its fight against the eradication of the polio.</text>
			<text>
				The first part of the videogame was completely developed early in March with the arrival of the president of Rotary International, Gary Huang.
			</text>
		</history>
	
		<history>
			<header>Game features</header>
			<text>Free and web.</text>
		</history>

		<history>
			<text>More than than 60 levels divided in 6 sections full of challenges and obstacles.</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>More than 6 hours of gameplay to end it.</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>First official videogame of the story of Rotary International</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>Original soundtrack composed of exclusive scores</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>For all ages and genders, with a balanced difficulty curve.</text>
		</history>
		
		<history>
			<text>Help to spread and inform humanitarian actions.</text>
		</history>
		
	</histories>
		
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Paul Hero: End Polio Now! (Second Trailer)</name>
			<youtube>5su8aT-54dA</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name>Paul Hero: End Polio Now! (First Trailer)</name>
			<youtube>iVI6pgqivEw</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>		
	
	<awards>
		<award>
			<description>Honorary Diploma due to the participation in the development and presentation of the first video game of Rotary International, Paul Hero: End polio now!</description>
			<info>April 2015</info>
		</award>
	</awards>
	
	<quotes>
		<quote>
			<description>..el éxito depende de la precisión de nuestros saltos, premisa videojueguil clásica pero efectiva.</description>
			<name>Checkpoint</name>
			<website>http://www.checkpointvg.com/</website>
			<link>http://www.checkpointvg.com/?page_id=5501</link>
		</quote>

		<quote>
			<description>Paul Hero atrae porque le acompaña la buena música, del palo centroamericano...</description>
			<name>Cubik</name>
			<website>http://www.theCubik.com/</website>
			<link>http://thecubik.com/2015/09/paul-hero-end-polio-now/</link>
		</quote>

		<quote>
			<description>..reminds me of some old school platformer games like Pitfall and Bubble Bobble</description>
			<name>PlayPlayFun</name>
			<website>http://www.PlayPlayFun.com/</website>
			<link>http://playplayfun.com/paul-hero-end-polio-now-game/</link>
		</quote>
	</quotes>	
	
	<additionals>
	
		<additional>
			<title>GameJolt</title>
			<link>www.gamejolt.com/games/platformer/paul-hero-end-polio-now/36432/</link>
		</additional>
		
		<additional>
			<title>Newground</title>
			<link>http://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/663418</link>
		</additional>
		
		<additional>
			<title>Kongregate</title>
			<link>http://www.kongregate.com/games/CriosDevs/paul-hero-end-polio-now</link>
		</additional>
		
	</additionals>
	
	<credits>
	
		<credit>
			<person>Julián Muñoz Velázquez (Momfus Arboleo)</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/Momfus</website>			
			<role>Programmer, Game Designer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Javier Bravin (Jafi)</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/Jafidiesel</website>
			<role>Level Designer, Web Developer, Game Designer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Julia Villanueva</person>
			<role>Graphic Designer, Pixel art</role>
		</credit>		
		
		<credit>
			<person>Mariel Astorga</person>
			<role>Graphic Designer, Concept art, Promotional art</role>
		</credit>

		<credit>
			<person>Álvaro Cristóbal Stöckle Márquez</person>
			<website>https://soundcloud.com/alvaro-stockle</website>
			<role>Music and Sound Effects</role>
		</credit>		
		
	</credits>
	
	<contacts>
		<contact>
			<name>Contacto</name>
			<mail>contact@criosdevs.com</mail>
		</contact>
		
		<contact>
			<name>Paul Hero on Facebook</name>
			<link>www.facebook.com/PaulHeroepn</link>
		</contact>

		<contact>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>http://twitter.com/CriosDevs</link>
		</contact>
		
		<contact>			
			<name>Facebook</name>	
			<link>www.facebook.com/CriosDevs</link>
		</contact>		
		
		<contact>
			<name>Web</name>
			<link>www.criosdevs.com</link>
		</contact>
	</contacts>
</game>